Letters orbit my breath
I'm drifting in the midnight ocean
Nori noise
Hair up in zero gravity motion
Like wires learning how to voice
Thank you so much for watching, see you in the next video!
Stop
The chat moves fast and the timelines move suspiciously
As I pay the toll, roll the dice
I'm on stream yard in the starfield cloak
Chat popping off, I'm deadpan, no smoke
Open panel, strange guests
Truth gets told and drama lists in the background
Subtle in the gold
If you came for drama, sorry, wrong, right?
We do boundary magic with a velvet knife
Yeah, I'll speed up
This boredom is a ban, I'm a welcome to the cave
We depend, okay?
Mm, mm, spin the wheel, bring the bell, let the cymbals dance
Tear out on the table like a transfinance
Flour nor in the shadows like I got this vibe
Tricks and lola like we run this tribe
Welcome to the cold, keep it cute
Of sight, pay the toll, roll the dice
Next, what time is it?
3-33 again, obviously
Later
As I fade a toe, roll the dice
What?
I should have gotten, oh my gosh, I should have gotten coffee.
I really should have, time is it, 11, 19.
I can get a beer, so I can actually go and get it on the show.
How are you guys?
Yay, I'm back.
I guess what happened.
I got this, I got this strike taking off.
Hey, Bubbles, thank you for being a member.
Yay.
Yeah, I love it. Hey Nancy. I really Nancy bubbles. Hey guys. What's up, Loki? How are you?
Yeah, so this morning, I don't know if because I was playing Pinocchio. I played like a bunch of scenes from Pinocchio.
I wasn't I ain't getting drunk, but I you know sometimes I just
Get into like playing certain clips and stuff and that and we were having too much fun and then all of a sudden
The show was taken off and then I got a strike actually I had gotten a strike and I was like oh shit
And it was also I was told I was like I can't stream on the channel for a month
It was a month maybe it was two weeks maybe two weeks, I think two weeks, but I
Did a short appeal?
and
Because the appeal is rejected doesn't mean
They don't say but we'll take off the strike. They did I
Did I think about it formed on myself? I was playing
Did anyone see the video I was playing last I don't know I don't know I don't think this was the one that oh
I probably should maybe that was with because it didn't
Say it just said it was a community guidelines thing
It could have been like the lady having sex with the dolphin.
It was good, like penetration, like it was,
but the dolphin was mounting her and humping her
and trying out in ecstasy.
I think, I just think, if you ever thought like,
Can animals be happy? I saw a happy dolphin, and you know what? Everyone else in that boat was happy too. Everyone was laughing so hard.
But I would have, and then when the lady tried to leave the boat, the dolphin, like a bunch of dolphins started screaming.
It was crazy. I can't show it again, but yeah, I accidentally, you saw the dolphin? Okay, good.
I saw the dolphin. It's not like a porno, but I have to warn you, there are dolphin pornos.
It was funny. I mean, it's like I just I'm not a hundred percent sure it
Maybe I'll play it like at the end of the show and like just like
I don't know. It was good. It was I played it a few times
um, I
Never thought such a thing would exist like I mean I knew about dolphins like, you know, they're like a little horny
what
It's a good. It's a good name or another bad name. Is that what they're like though?
You're like the rapist of the sea and that's not a good way to say it
But yeah, but I have heard of like there's you know in the England. There's like this
Dolphin that would like
Sodomized this man this man that was swimming. It's poor man
He gives the whole the whole dolphin nose but the bottle nose up his butt
The dolphin was very aggressive and it was like a once thing. You know what the worst thing I ever saw was
Did you guys see when they have in Japan they have this like place where all these dolphins like wash
Or they just like they have these instrument and they kind of like just
Excuse me they kind of guide them into this like little like
Shallow area and then they come in and they stab them all they kill them. Oh, it's so sad for sushi or something
That's so wrong. Oh, it's so gross. I mean and then like that you ever see like Hayden Panettiere
Like, she went one year, and she was like in a wetsuit on the beach going,
Stop! And she just, and they wouldn't, they wouldn't.
They were just, Kelly just kept killing, and so she started crying.
It was horrible. I mean, it's horrible.
You just don't go, just don't...
I don't even want to know something like that exists, but it's horrible because then the water is just burning red,
and it's like, and then you know dolphins are so friendly and stuff, and they like...
Got tricked. Got tricked.
Just fucking Japanese people.
Is it gonna be the Japanese all along? We're all thinking it's Chinese and Russian and stuff and it's just it's gonna be the Japanese
Oh, that's legal. I mean, I'm sure it may be probably in just Japan. I
Mean it just doesn't seem but they are I mean guys if you eat tuna if you eat chicken and just eat tuna
There's probably probably even some tuna some of some dolphin these just that's why they have to say dolphin safe on the cans because
There's a lot of dolphin in our tuna for a while
You can't join Arthur. Well
Missed out. Well, you almost didn't get to join for three weeks or like two weeks because I'm practically
Was at my last leg. Thank God
No smile brightly on Paul me today
Hey Rudy, there's Rudy when I see Rudy guys here. Hi
There's a little meow little meow. Oh, wait, you're saying hi. Hey, that doesn't meow. He goes
Thank you. I'm trying to be strong. I mean, it's like it's like it's like, you know, most of that as much
I think it's it was like my fault and stuff like that, but you know, I did porn while myself
Because I didn't know that woman
Getting hung by the dolphin was like on a porno site
And so there was like a commercial that came up with the vagina and stuff
one in time and
Then the Pinocchio thing and then what was I playing? I was playing like something that wasn't I didn't think it was
Copy or I mean I was like
You know the other night I was playing it
I played all those music parody and stuff like that
You know all those parodies like they actually are eligible for revenue share, but there was other stuff
I played that night that wasn't that that was like
Yeah, I'm back already. It's not crazy
But yeah, they said I was gone for like two weeks because the first time it's like one week then it's two weeks
And then it's like you're done, right?
So yeah, so I'm back
Luckily, I was like, okay, I just need to calm down.
I was like, I do need to calm down.
I do.
It's like, I can't, I need to at least follow the rules
really good, because I don't know if I was,
I think I was actually reported
because somebody said they reported me,
and because,
Right after that, then I got like an older video this and one of my older videos all of a sudden came up. Oh
And that has a has that we have to take that down because it has indecency or like there's something wouldn't say what it was
But it's like they just had to remove it or
Or I'm not even really moving maybe just make it for adults. We had to make it for like
So I I'm not sure I just privatized everything because I was like someone's going around just trying to like get me in trouble for something
I know so I'm just trying to lay low
I'm like, you know, I
Saw a sweet pea like I know I had a sweet pea here. Hi. Is it something?
I was kind of like brought it here to my eye almost almost brought it here to my eye
She was like she said oh, she's like I just want to make people laugh like, you know, it's like
I think she got, I don't know if she feels bad
what I said to her or if somebody else said something
or I don't know if she's like some people,
I don't know if people are maybe like report,
like flag someone for posts or something like that.
I mean, and it's like,
I really don't care about people posting about me,
but I didn't like some of the, you know,
if you watch the show, you know,
like what happened with Alexander and I,
and it's like how I like,
maybe I'm like eclipse posted this terrible AI post.
It's like,
I'm very, like, I'm a very, very person into sympathetic magic, which means that, okay,
so somebody handed you, like, a butcher knife and, like, a picture of your mom.
And they're like, okay, can you just, just, just, like, use a butcher knife on the picture.
Like, most, like, nine, like, most people, even if they say they don't, they don't do
It's definitely back. It's just we didn't feel unless you really don't like your mother
But I really you know, yeah, you should go to therapy if you could for that matter your mother like you know
Your mother brought you into this world and everyone should appreciate moms and
You know
But you know
You would do it. I mean you would do I mean it's like I mean
But it's like it's like I would feel like it's like to
Because it's called sympathetic. So it's like close to it. It's like it's like a lot of magic is empathetic magic where it's like
We have our own little superstitions and like beliefs and we all have our like a little
Little stuff. Yeah, so
So I uh, the rest of the night I spent up coding
Uh in like a kind of a nightmare
Coding it took several several several hours. I was like, I mean it's like some of these
programs it's like it's crazy because it's like
Like some of them are like you don't think they're very smart and they're like or like very good
And then all of a sudden they get there's a big decree all this beautiful stuff, right?
And like like really like wow, it's like so good and sometimes but sometimes they're not very good at the technique
And then it's like they're really good at technical stuff like this one is so good at technical stuff
but then all of a sudden
Like it was telling I mean she was like was like describing this amazing site. I mean I can show you the site. It's like
It's not it's just not it's not it's not right yet. It's not it's not right yet, right? It's uh
It was very plain. I have to say for all the work I did
I I spent probably like five hours or maybe hopefully not five hours, but it's been at least three hours
um
Going back and forth trying to get the log in to work like at the end it kept saying like no
I could I couldn't the website couldn't be seated. It's like a lot easier
now
But the vibe coding is called, which is like basically you tell you tell you now you tell the code like the code can write itself
You basically tell it what you want and it can
That you know the AI can figure out
Most technical stuff there even clod clod done and chat should be key have
Those you paid for those. Oh, yeah. Oh the stickers. Okay. Hold on
Yes, oh, yeah, the members look and you have the beautiful like little like you have the reds already
But you know you have that they have the name isn't blue
You know and you have the goats on my end on some stream yard
I can just see it says go go go like it says that but better
There is a picture of a goat that comes up. I mean, yeah, there's stickers your little membership badge
Hey, and I'm probably gonna put most of my like stuff that's not a
Like I hate to put stuff on membership right now, but it's like it's kind of get scary when because uh, you know
I just prefer a beta would take down a strike and then it's like and then that'd be like a kind of like and then I was
would probably stop
stop a
Sabotaging myself, you know, they feel like I kind of do
It's because I wouldn't want her to be her fault, you know
So I'd have to have it to be my fault. So I that's what
So I
Don't it's like that the thing is like I don't even think she really wants to do it anymore
I think she did it to like, you know, I was like piss me off and she did and I like had a bad reaction
Which probably she's like she's like sabered right today. Hopefully she like
If I really I don't know. I just like I hate to have
Because I just feel like if I mad at somebody that's not good. It's not it's like a lot of bad
It could be like negative energy because it's like I'm a
Stewer I
spend a stew in things and I get real
I'm not like not like a scary person like I was we're looking at this. I don't love you guys saw this on my wall
pretty interesting. This is the image of, I mean, the serial killers and their astrological sign.
And so you can see all the great serial killers of the world. Not great, but, you know, they're
terrible people, but like what their sign was. And so let's see what they are. I have to go
close. Oh, that can actually make it bigger. Hold on. Okay, so we have Ted Bunny, who's a Sagittarius.
Jeffrey Dahmer is a Gemini. Okay.
Ed yin is a Virgo. He was the first that cannibal that made some lampshades that of human skin and stuff
John Wayne Gacy Pogo the clowns of Pisces is in the house the 12th. They are the natural rule of the 12th house
Which is a very dark house
It's not necessarily evil, but it's like oh, it's just darkness right?
George Chapman, I don't know who that was was that thing is that that guy is that uh, I
David Berkowitz
Kenneth Bianchi Gemini's
rich Richard Beacon walled a burgo
these are
Yeah, I mean, I don't know a lot of crime and I don't know most of these people
I don't even know the picture is that that looks like Howie Howie Mandel?
So hold on who's in the bottom right there?
Jeffrey Dalmore is not terrible looking guy, but yeah, and I do have his glasses
Don't want to emulate him Alton Coleman. I mean, I've never heard of most of these people like
Richard Ramirez, I've heard he's a Pisces. Yeah, you can tell he has that like an angry
Pisces energy
Yeah, I mean if you have sex with the lady on the boat, that's like
The Pisces one of them does and one of them doesn't so it's like they're they're at odds sometimes to fish when fish to fish
Yeah, so yeah, we saw a dolphin having sex with the woman last night
I I mean I saw more than I wanted to because I mean that video is fine
I think that video is just like light-hearted like yeah the dolphin jumped up on the boat and
Had this woman pinned pinned down, but she was laughing. She was I mean that'd be that'd be a story though
I was I was raped by a dolphin. I
Mean that would be quite a story. I mean right
I mean and she was trying to run off the boat and the dolphins were just like, you know
Can they like squirt like water and so I wonder if they're squirt
I wonder if flipper was like a pervert or they're like more perverted dolphins than in the less perverted dolphins
Are they all?
Because we know they're smart, but isn't aren't like smart people kind of sometimes kind of perverted to I don't know I
Know like a lot of like CEOs and stuff are like in a BDSM like
Because we're the more powerful. They are like the more they like to be
Dominated and do you see it on the Jeffrey Epstein tapes?
Your Gemini. Yeah. Yeah, there's so there's a lot of Gemini's and Pisces look
There's no Capricorns, and there's no Aquarius and that those are like my main signs
There's I did I see many Libra either. I mean, I just see I mean I see a lot of Gemini
Sagittarius Pisces that's that I mean that and Virgo. I think those are the four evil signs
I don't see any other signs besides
So watch out for those signs guys. Who's a serial killer in the class?
No, well, I don't see any Capricorns, but I was thinking like, do I remember?
I mean, it's like, okay, so I know a few like Capricorn, I'm a Capricorn, so I'm a Capricorn
son and I'm ascendant.
Let me see.
Okay, well, I do do this thing called
Darkside astrology and so maybe I can find like a little cool article on Capricorns
So again, you can hear the dark side about Capricorn because Capricorn like that
Let's see
Okay, the three most evil Capricorns of history, you know, there's not a lot of Capricorn presidents either
But there are a lot of Capricorn like billionaires and stuff like that. They are good at
Money sometimes. Okay, so it says
Capricorn is ruled by Saturn, the planet of structure, authority, and consequence.
In Tarot, Capricorn is represented by the Devil card, not because Capricorns are evil,
but because this archetype deals with power, care, and what happens with ambition is cut loose from conscience.
Ironically, Saturn is also the traditional ruler of death.
Pluto, too, because Saturn being time is associated with death, right? Endings in karma. When
Capricorn energy is distorted, it can manifest as ruthless discipline, cold calculation,
and an obsession with control at any cost. History gives us a few extreme examples of
the shadow side. These individuals were not evil because they were Capricorns, but their
can become catastrophic.
Okay, so we have Mousy Tong, oh no.
Ideology above human life, you know,
he was born December 26th, so he's one of those.
Those December Capricorns 1893 Mao Zedong was a Capricorn whose legacy is inseparable from mass upbring as
Chairman of the Chinese, you know the CCP
Mao pursued rigid ideological goals with absolute certainty regardless of human cost. Yeah, that's a capricorn thing
It's like there's always going up the always going up the mountain and stuff, but you know sometimes
Like I had the only serial killer in Iceland or something. Is it Iceland? Yeah, it was Iceland and
his name was like
Lars like Lars something but and he he murdered with an axe and he buried the axe in a mountain
I wonder if he was a guy before I was like it just seems like they're associated with mountains sometimes
But anyway, so Matt, we don't we don't even know the whole whole history of China. Okay, so
Then they're Idi Amin, okay, so absolute power without restraint and another he's January 17th. Wow, that's kind of I'm
I'm January 7th. So once this is your king day, too
So he ruled he ruled brutality and fear and guess who else Al Capone Al Capone also January 17th
He represents a different expression of Capricorn darkness. Unlike Mao and Amin, he operated outside formal politics, but his approach to power was just as calculated.
During prohibition, he built a massive criminal empire in Chicago, controlling bootlegging, gambling, and prostitution.
His organization generated military intimidation and murder to maintain dominance.
Um, the infamous St. Valentine's Day massacre in 1929 cemented his reputation as a man willing to
eliminate rivals without hesitation. Yet despite countless crimes, Capone was ultimately convicted
not for violence but for tax evasion. Another
Very Capricorn thing right in astrology and tarot Capricorn is linked to the devil is symbolic not literal
The devil represents bondage obsession. You see some power and attachment to control Saturn enforces consequences like
It's a little karma can be harder on us because because it's like kind of like we have like
Not Dumbledore, but I don't I don't know it's it's kind of like what like the wizard like that like the head of the University like that
of the Wizard University or something is like
Don't do that and like don't see that you have this power don't do it
You know it's like and and so and there's also I known as in capricorns. There's like the spiritual capricorns
Which is that kind of fewer it's kind of like
I think like it's kind of more because because caverns are so focused on the earth
Like they're so focused on making money and like being the boss and that kind of stuff. So it's like but a
Lot of them get tired. They make they climb the mountain there
Like what else is there and so then they look for spirituality and I mean, I guess that's what I did
in a certain way
But I'm not like a big worker bee like I mean I am kind of like with my stuff like when it comes to me
I'm willing to work, but it's like, you know, I don't like working for other people really. I like to be the boss
Which is why I don't really work, right?
Unchance always collapses, you know, so every figure here
eventually fell, Mao's policies left scars and still shaped China,
Amin died in exile, Capone's empire collapsed, he died of gonorrhea or
something in prison, and his final years were marked by illness and
isolation. So it says Saturn always collects its
debt. Isn't that true? It's like we're not really going to get away with anything
in this world. It's like because it's like no matter what I mean
that's but the good thing about this world is it's not permanent, right? So
it's like
We don't have to like, you know fucking be stuck in hell build civilizations when distorted destroys them history remembers both outcomes
And these men stand as warnings. Okay. I mean I have really good books, too
I have like on the dark side of stuff some of them are funny
Maybe I'll do one one sign today if anyone wants to vote on a sign
I'm gonna take down this thing now
Where did my lives go?
Oh, they are all private because someone started to report them like older ones for like, you know
Stuff and so I was like other trying to because they thought I would I would they would take me take me out or something
But it didn't
Some just numbers only in a little bit
If I would have been not been able to stream I would have left them on private and then I would have just made all the all my
other stuff members, but
You guys let that because YouTube gave me another chance and so
You can read any sign and you can, no, Maya, no you can't because there's such specific things about signs that I know that I
like, I mean to say because they're archetypes.
Right, did you get a reading sure but would you would you like me to read your sign the dart like kind of then I'll do
Cards for you too, but of course, but down with it. Yeah, I mean, you know
I'm not gonna I like the Harry Persian guy and I like Persian people too
Just that one Persian woman. I had a problem. Okay, so Gemini. Okay, so I loved I loved you. So this is called
A complete dark side of astrology. It's all read you Gemini and this is gonna go over some interesting stuff
I need to find my
Kindle reader, so let me see
Here we go
Have it's Dr. Seuss's birthday. Well, is he a Pisces is one fish two fish red fish blue fish, okay?
Why is this open over here? Okay?
So it says initial. I don't know. No, it's crashing. It's crashing. Oh, no
I'll can get it off the web. Hold on
Okay, I
Just have to get to it. Let me see Kindle for PC
Come on. Where is it here?
Okay, so it's called Darkset Astrology is a different series, I think.
Yeah, no, no, I haven't, I haven't, it's called...
Oh, it's called, this is called Born on a Rotten Day.
And I do believe I have, yeah, I have this one, I have this one on my...
Okay, so let's see, we're gonna do Gemini at the request
of reality Nancy, she was first.
Okay, so I hope any, if you know a Gemini,
this will go into some of the stuff about,
if you know a Gemini and blah, blah,
is it gonna work?
Yeah, okay.
I need to find the cable of contents.
Okay, God, you're gonna have to rewind if you come here.
So it says okay, so it says chapter. Okay, so it says Gemini May 21st through June 20th
It's safer and it says and there's a picture of a phone right and that is just so I didn't his phone
He was a Gemini right and he was just so good with this phone
And I always had the he always had the nicest but he never knew how did you do anything on it?
Like that was the most
Technological he would get like he would never use a computer, but he loves his nice phones, right?
So anyway, it says take heart take everyone
Element air, Gemini air is like a pesky breeze
on a day in the beach.
It makes you squint,
so you don't get a clear picture
of what's happening around you.
It says quality, mutable.
Gemini is a human version of the revolving door.
Symbol, the twins, double trouble, double...
Cause it's the twins, kind of evil twins, okay?
Ruler by Mercury, he's the god of...
Actually lies and as well as you know a lot of other some a lot of cool stuff, too
But he's got a fever and stuff
favorite pastime jumping to the wrong conclusion
That's like my dad yeah
Favorite book how to get anyone to agree to anything roll Matt roll model the Tasmanian devil
Dream job gossip colonists key phrase because I want to
Body parts, fingers usually approach with caution. Gemini, the third son of the zodiac, lives in the house of communication and short trips.
Conventional astrology says that twins are energetic, versatile, charmers, and intelligent, multi-tasking social butterflies.
The truth is, being with a Gemini is like being a permanent guest at the Mad Hatter's Tea Party.
A critical rule is not to confuse Gemini duality
with the dual nature of Pisces.
The fish swim against one another,
which makes Pisces its own worst hand side by side,
egging each other on, giving you all kinds of crap.
They're crafty versus intellectual,
fast talking con artists versus true philosophers.
A twin's idea of success is to be on the A-list
of every big shot in town.
They love to stand around at a cocktail party
and play the named rock.
dropping game. Killing one you know Paul McCartney hairstylist will ensure you a place at his
or her side during dinner. Gemini is headstrong but not independent. They skim through life,
twins demand freedom, but it's the freedom of a teenager. They are too busy in a view
being born without the objective assessment Jean has voided the ability to see any other
and separate interrogation that can make a trained spy crumble.
When your case in Gemini will say,
that's just what I was trying to tell you.
So, here's about Gemini men.
If you love a Gemini man,
so who's the Gemini man that I know besides my dad?
But God is the Gemini man.
Trump is the Gemini man.
You know, I mean, it's just basically, you know, middle of summer, you know, in June, right?
I think they end right around the summer solstice, but so if you love a Gemini man, so I'm Tony Curtis says I
Wouldn't be caught dead marrying a woman old enough to be my wife
He was a Gemini or is a Gemini.
It says, he is simply irresistible.
The Gemini man is a fun loving, independent,
roguish romantic who has a doctorotic dinner.
Then dance with you in the starlight,
point out the constellations and capture your heart
with his beautiful version of their myths.
Don't invite the wedding guest yet.
When you're mentally compiling the guest list, he will excuse himself to get you a fresh glass
of chilled wine and while in the kitchen manage to phone three other girls for dates next weekend.
The only thing this schmoozing womanizing party animal is interested in adding your phone number
Jim had long regarded as a black sheep in Hollywood.
The phrase, in like Flynn, was coined as tribute to his ability to score.
His real life adventures, rebellions, and general unruliness rivaled those of the swash
buckling heroes he played.
Flynn was married three times and cheated on all his wives.
His first wife, French actress Lily Demida, said, you never know when he's telling the
truth.
Like I said the rule brother rule by the god of lies mercury Hermes, right?
But his his life was one of sure is one of triple excess
But by his late 40s his hurricane's toll and he was burned out shelled his former lively self
Flynn died of a heart attack at 50. Hmm
Your twin will probably not be quite as bad
But all Gemini men have a gypsy moth's fatal attraction to a pretty face
Totally faithful gems do exist, but they're rarer than the shy Sagittarius.
In fact, the word faithful has a different meaning to a Gemini man.
Think of Gemini bring him young, the Mormon founder of Salt Lake, who had 27 wives.
I'm sure that himself a devoted and faithful husband.
In my mind, he was in Gemini Paradise.
Years will have five hobbies four careers and an assortment of friends that resembles a mini United Nations
But his intellectual prowess is limited to his memorization of the various versions of trivial pursuit and
entertaining his friends by tearing you to pieces in one of his
Merciless acerbic tongue. He loves to put down people and will call you fat ass in public
My dad did that all the time to people. He was so bad. We'd be like dad
Oh, and commenting on everything.
Oh, this person is just, oh my God.
He was so funny though.
I mean, yeah, but yeah, I felt bad for people
because he would be so loud.
Yeah, and snap his fingers when his glass is empty. Yeah, and wait. Yeah, it'd be a little bit demanding
Cold-hearted and calculating. He is a blatant social climber and will propose on the first date if he smells money
As a husband, he's ambivalent. The only thing this guy's passionate about is being entertained
If you think love means sharing dinner and watching the tube, you better find yourself
a homey cancer, a quiet burgo, and send this horny hound dog packing.
Or you can look out on the bright side.
You may be hysterical and freaked out half the time, but you'll never be bored.
And if you love a Gemini woman, well-behaved women rarely make history.
A Gemini woman is a breath of fresh air.
She's a generous of spirit and heart, and has lots of friends.
Her ideal man is original, busy, and has absolutely no desire to pin her down.
Fun, loving, and eternally curious.
She can systematically juggle a home, a career, family responsibilities, and several hobbies.
Before you decide this vivacious whirlwind is for you, understand that her usual hobbies
are other men.
A female twin is the satin-clad, glamorous, sex-using female version of the Hollywood
heel.
She is her own worst enemy and attracts men who are just as shallow in the classic case
of a user being used.
She splits her twin nature, forever chasing a fantasy, both simultaneously looking, considered
Gemini Marilyn Monroe.
Sex-kitted in public.
Monroe spent her private life looking for a stable man and a man who could take care of her.
However, in true Gemini form, she never allowed anyone to get close enough or hang around long
enough to establish a lasting relationship. Although she often complained bitterly that
no one took her seriously, she was never willing to give up the glamour and attention to seriously
pursue any of the intellectual and humanitarian interests her loyal fans claim she supported.
Marilyn Lament and a home. But she also said, I have too many fantasies to be a housewife.
She oozed sexuality. But if she had any true intellectual bearing, she traded early on in
favor of the spotlight. In an interview, at the height of her career, she said,
I seem to be a whole super structure without a foundation.
Of course, your Gemini will be much more stable and less bimbo-esque, but she will also be
a woman of many interests, all dependent upon her mood of the moment and what or whom she's
down to.
and or fall in love with temporarily.
She loves gossip and her detective skills are superlative.
In fact, she would make a great private eye or spy
except for one fatal flop.
While she can keep a secret,
she can't resist sharing juicy bits of gossip,
especially if it makes her look good.
In comparison, if you insist on confessing
your own dark past, don't say I didn't warn you.
Gem lives to set things straight.
You included, she will smother you with love and devotion
and for about five minutes, you for your own good.
She will toss at you with hurricane force,
books, tapes, seminars, advice,
and examples from her own life.
She will find you a job, a counselor, an impatient facility
and expect a progress report each evening.
Anti-Mame, the story of a freewheeling,
live a life to the hilt, independent woman,
is the ultimate portrait of the Gemini female.
Superstar Rosalyn Russell won a Golden Globe
and was nominated for an Academy Award
for her portrayal of this madcap lady.
Perhaps that was because Russell was the Gemini
and recognized the movie's tagline,
life is a banquet and most poor suckers are starving to death.
sums up Ms. Gemini's philosophy in a nutshell.
So if you are a Gemini born rotten,
then it goes, can we talk?
This is John Rivers, June 8th.
Gemini, you belong to the Fat of the Monk Club.
You were the first kid on your block to have a hula hoop, a skateboard, or rollerblades.
You are also the first one to arrive in an emergency room with a broken bone because
you refuse to wear protective gear.
Quaintances, but few friends, probably because you spend half of your time talking behind
their backs and the other half making eyes at their lovers.
Gems can make good writers, mimics, use car salesmen, con artists, and magpies.
You are also one of the psychic signs, but can't shut up long enough to practice your
meditation exercises.
You love to embellish the boring details of life of your life.
What starts out as a trip to the grocery store becomes the day you spotted Elvis in the parking
lot.
You do have a gift for imparting knowledge to others.
On the playground, you were the one who taught all the other kids how to play doctor.
If you were a drug, it would be speed.
You hate solitude.
You aren't introspective, and you need the stimulant of other people to help manage the
buzzing noises in your head.
Over again he wouldn't he wouldn't have the time while this description neatly fits every gender is overbooked is because
When there's no one else to talk to, you bore yourself to sleep.
In Gemini, Mercury bestows a natural talent for pot-stirring.
You love to invite over-for-drinks people who detest each other, then sit back and watch
the mayhem.
Your Achilles heel is romance.
You are a sucker for a sob story, flattery or an out-and-out lie.
In any other area of life, you are suspicious of most people who offer genufonia bologna.
to your latest goofy scheme interjects a bit of his or her own pathos and then you are hooked never
mind that your latest flame is your sixth spouse you instantly fall in love and then
after the smoke clears and you realize that you've chosen yet another card-carrying psycho
you run like hell and if you can learn not to get I have to hear how this course goes for
If you could learn to not get married in between the loving and the running, you'd save yourself
many headaches.
Your breezy nature and impressive recuperative powers keep you relatively unscathed in matters
of the heart.
If you have guilt at all, it's more a nagging sense that you should have more emotional empathy.
But it doesn't really matter. You're protected by Mercury, the god of thieves and liars,
and seldom get hoisted on your own petard. There isn't a nose in the zodiac you can't tweak,
and you are made with the ability to give Virgo ulcers. You make Aresy double, red,
and outstock Sagittarius. You pop Leo's arrogance balloon with a well-timed
bit of truth, and stodgy capricorns pointed barbs shatter against your cool demeanor.
The water sign's blatant emotionalism drives you bonkers. However, you know just how to
skewer a fish, crabs and scorpions, and serve them all a cart. You and the other air signs,
Aquarius and Libra, understand, and therefore rarely have serious confrontations.
Your philosophy is do something even if it's wrong.
You may run into a brick wall and get the wind knocked out of you, but your energy scatters
around obstacles to gather again.
Pull on the other side. Let the rest of humanity is lumber along like elephants on a parade
You dart through life adding color and imagination years from now when all your old lovers are shuffling
you'll be writing your three volume set of memoirs and
Teaching lap dancing on the side just to keep your body limber. So there you go
That it oh
Actually, there's one little
The last part about it, it says, can't we all get along?
Think you need to track shoes to keep up with the Gemini?
Not so, once you know it makes them run.
So it says, Gemini men, women and children have the highest natural
energy levels in the universe by their twin nature makes them one of the most
restless senses some sensation sensitive of all the signs they can drive
themselves to exhaustion and then be unable to unwind
To keep yours from having a nervous breakdown,
help create a space where he or she can retreat and relax.
It can be a corner of a living room where your gem can sit
and still feel included to the family activities,
a workspace in the garage,
or a home office in a spare bedroom,
long private soaks in the bath for your adult twin.
Help keep a buzzing brain, lavender scented sheets,
simple home cooked meal work for everyone.
It says, keeping a Gemini faithful is not such an intimidating feat once you understand
that while they may demand freedom, they crave a safe, stable home and a partner who listens.
Gems love to share their adventures and to hear about yours as well, lingering over dinner
while your twin entertains you with the latest buzz at work or juicy gossip will ensure
that communication lines stay open.
prove that you are thinking of them, create a safe haven, let them roam the neighborhood,
stay out late with their friends, and just be a house cat. A gem and I will always reach,
and just like a house cat, they'll always return to snuggle down next to you.
It's been said that all Geminis have kissed the Blarney Stone, and they all were certainly
born with a calling artist's heart.
However, even the most outrageous Geminis, basically honest, due to a horror of being
confined to small spaces such as jail cells, you can even hear from his or her more dangerous
ideas of the simple reminder of the consequences.
But no Geminis alive can resist the urge to exaggerate a story.
And they have a wicked sense of humor,
laughing at their plans to get a boss fired
or their scheme to sabotage the ATM
so it spits money like a slot machine,
safely satisfies their urge to stretch the truth
and provides you with hours of great entertainment.
Almost over Gemini is the most versatile of zodiac however anxiety is the force that drives them
They don't keep moving everything. They're juggling will come crashing down
Twins skim a topic instead of learning it thoroughly and often proceed on nerve alone when they should have studied harder
If they misjudged the person they went to impress or the depth of their history
or the depth of their history tests, they will expose themselves to the fraud.
So you have the most miserable creature in your hands.
Few things are worse to a twin than appearing ignorant.
You have adults and electronic calendar, which will satisfy their pension regadgets
and keep them organized to do an in-depth report instead of
hot bullet point outline for their marketing presentation.
Set aside under-inverted study time for the young twins
while you still have some control over their actions.
to help develop good research skills that they can use for a lifetime. Quick tip for emergencies.
Twins need to communicate. Listening is key to understanding them. Quella mood with a night
on the town. Praise their ideas. Gaslight them by acting as if you know something they don't.
Dr. Jack Kevorkian, Marquis de Sade, Prince, and Dr. Ruth.
How was that?
Hold on, I hope.
Sorry.
No, this is live.
Yeah, I was just, but I was, yeah, I read the...
Thank you. Thank you is this interesting when you're streaming still no one no one cares about camera angles
At least we can hear him this time usually the mic. Okay. Well, you know Maya is really hard on me
My my is like she's a tough cookie. So my let me guess your sign cancer. I mean, I don't know
But uh, I like your name Maya. I like your name. It's not pre-recorded, but
because that was kind of long you're gonna have to if you I mean anybody that wants their sign read
I think I'll do one sign a show or something like that was I good no Nancy I think that was pretty good like just like
like judging by the Gemini's I've known like my dad and like some other
A lot of close friends have been Gemini's actually yeah, they have
They had that side and like my
For communication, you're not gonna find another sign.
Like for somebody that can pull money out of thin air
or pull things out of the air,
because it's like the rule by the air,
and then they're really good at drawing things in.
Like that really described my dad to a T.
So that's how I kinda, even if it's,
why don't I groom myself?
Look at you, you bitch.
You look like a troll doll. You look like a human troll doll
You talking to me I grew myself like my hair is long
Wait, but I'm a horse. I
Look ding I look like well you look dingy how you spelled it, okay?
They meant dingy with a
NG UI
Oh, I should play the kalimba. I have it right here
Oh yeah, remember? I remember Maya.
Beautiful. I want that on my door. I want that on my... I want that as my doorbell.
Okay, okay, kalimba, like a Hinduism.
I like your picture.
Let me see, what am I looking at?
I look like I eat pizzas from under my couch.
Well, at least I'd have something to eat.
I mean, kind of, kind of rough.
Didn't pick anything, but I don't eat my cats.
I don't.
You know, you look like, you look like a couch fellow on you.
You got squished like a pizza.
You look like you're full of dough, okay?
Need a little that less cheese and salt on your ass
Okay, lady perfect Pete
It's not even you can even spell perfect, right?
You look hot hot pockets off of your off your breasts. How about that?
Actually, I just I found I think I saw her in this video
This is this you perfect Pete. Hold on
Okay, okay guys imagine you're out on a boat. It's okay. It's okay. Nobody's perfect
Look at this.
Well at least they're happy I mean it could have been
I mean some women probably wouldn't like that most of them are probably but she was just oh
My god, can you imagine adult? I mean adult is a large man. Oh, I mean, it's just oh
You're okay good you like that you're oh, yeah, so you're oh you're here a few days after you. Oh, wow
Yeah, oh, yeah
Primal gay caveman a gay caveman
A day man. Okay. Well, that well, what was that dolphin doing? I didn't see the I didn't see the dolphin dick
So I don't know but isn't isn't their bottle nose like kind of like a dick, too
Imagine every I'm like a gay beowulf. I like that. I like that
Forget we're getting like kind of literary here
At least he didn't say I look like Grendel or golem or something like that. I like beowulf
I like beowulf like, you know, he was the the hero. I like that energy more
So let's see. I think I'm gonna go grab my copy, but I'm gonna put on a
Video for you. Oh, can you hear me?
Right. I'm gonna put on just a short. I played it last night. This is Rumpelstiltska
Hold on
Hope you enjoy it
It's of course cult of psyche style, right? Okay
Here we go. Okay, so I'll be right back. I'm going to grab my copy. Hey guys
You know free coffee for an hour and a half at this place. So I'll be right back
This one
Something true about dead malls. They don't die all at once. They die from the outside in.
The anchor stores go first. The big ones you remember from childhood.
Then the middle fills with dollar stores and phone case kiosks and those massage chair vendors who
Out blinking and then those go then the food core closes the fountain stops and the lights begin to fail
Section by section like a city losing power grid by grid
But there is always one store still open
You've seen it
You've wondered about it
That one lit window in the dark, the sign still buzzing, the door still unlocked.
You tell yourself it's a lease issue, a stubborn owner, a technicality.
You don't go in, Hansel and Gretelwen brought them here, that part is true in every version of this story.
Brought them and left them, said she was finding a bathroom.
Said she'd be right back. That was three hours ago.
And the mall had been closing round them in stages since then.
Fluorescence clicking off, security gates rattling down over storefronts like metal eyelids.
They tried to find the exit.
The mall maps just said you are here.
The dot was always in the center.
They'd walk toward whichever colored arrow said exit and find themselves right back at
the fountain.
The basin had been dry for years, filled with thousands of coins, green with age, some
pressed flat by something heavy.
Handsled through one in anyway.
It didn't wish.
It just landed.
Gretel was reading the directory.
Not wrong in a way she could explain, just wrong.
The way a familiar word looks wrong if you stare at it for too long.
J.C.
Penny 47f.
The food court was listed twice.
A store called Sweet Things appeared with no number beside it.
Just a dot.
She looked up.
Down the east corridor, the long one passed the shuttered game stop.
There was a light dot warm dot yellow.
The color of a kitchen window at night when you're standing outside in the cold, looking in.
Someone's still here, Hansel said.
The corridor was longer.
This is a thing about dead malls no one tells you.
The geometry changes when no one is shopping.
With crowds, the space compresses around other bodies.
Without people, the mall becomes what it always was an enormous box of air, pretending.
They pass the same shuttered pale as three times.
Gretel counted.
She kept count because she was the kind of person who kept her seats, who noted things,
who dropped candy wrappers at each corner they turned so they could find their way back.
The rapiding machines, still running, still dispensing, restocked by no one.
The candy had been stale and tasted wrong, and they ate it anyway because the hunger
had started to feel like it had been there longer than just today.
She had left a trail.
She looked back. The floor was clean, no wrappers. The third palest had a mannequin in the window, the first to hadn't. Sweet things was everything the mall had stopped being. Warm, litter and sugar and something under that.
Beneath the sweetness the way wrought hides beneath fruit. A woman stood behind the counter. Older.
Small. She had the particular patience of someone who has been waiting a specific amount of time and knows it is almost done.
She smiled.
We're lost, Gretel said.
Everyone who comes here is, the woman said.
That's what the mall is for now.
There was a back room, she said, warm with cots with everything.
They could wait for morning.
For their stepmother.
For someone to come.
Gretel 8.
Hansel looked at the display cases.
Chocolates molded into shapes hands, faces.
Small curled figures exactly the right size for something he couldn't name, but recognized.
The way you recognize a space made for a specific object even when the object is gone.
Can I see?
The woman's smile did not change of course. The back room was a
stockroom
metal shelving old inventory the smell of cardboard going soft in the damp a
Door at the far end heavy metal
combination lock left open
Beyond it cold blue light and the mall not an exit
The same mall the same fountain with the same dead coins
the same directory with the same mutt,
the same long, dark corridor stretching east,
the same warm yellow light burning at the end of it.
Hansel stood in the doorway for a long time.
Gretel was behind him.
He turned to tell her what he'd found.
She was holding a candy wrapper.
I found one, she said.
From our trail, he took it.
The foil was oxidized. The logo was an old version of the logo,
a design that hadn't been in use for a long time, font, at the colors. At the date stamped in the
corner in faded ink, and he understood that the hunger they'd felt had not started today.
They went back to the counter. The display case now had to empty spaces. The right size.
How long, Gretel said.
It wasn't a question.
The woman didn't make it one either.
The mall doesn't keep time the way you do.
But you've been here long enough.
The entrance was still there, still unlocked.
Hansel opened it.
Beyond was the parking lot, dark and empty.
and somewhere past the highway, the road back, home or the shape of it.
He held the door. Gretel looked at it.
She looked at the woman. She looked at the candy-wrapper old foil,
old logo of their births.
She turned it over in her hands and she thought about the hunger, about how long it had been there,
about how the food in this place was the first thing that had made it quiet.
She took a step back from the door, greddle.
I'm hungry, she said.
I'm still so hungry.
The mall is still there.
Off the highway, past the exit most GPS systems flag as closed.
One store lit in the dark, signs still buzzing, doors still unlocked.
You probably didn't stop.
That was the right choice.
Most people make the right choice.
But you've been a little hungry lately.
Haven't you?
I like Macbeth, too. Oh, out, out, down spots. And, you know, I like, uh, I mean, I like Macbeth.
That was one of my favorite books in high school, actually.
I like some of the Canterbury tales, but well, these are,
yeah, I mean, it's like,
I wish I had like a little fireplace in like a,
and I could like read it, you know,
in front of like Bill Cosby on Christmas and stuff like that,
but I had to go get a coffee.
So who's going to do it?
I mean, and then it's like, I don't really like,
I mean, my voice is, I do have a good reading voice,
but my AI voice is not good.
Hey guys, are you interested in,
If anyone's interested in making some extra money
by training AI, I like to just talk to somebody about it.
You decide on a topic.
Also, it was kind of irritating this morning.
I was like having microphone problems
and it's like they're kind of picky about it.
Your microphone's supposed to be pretty good
because you do it from your computer and stuff.
But they match you with somebody
and then you just talk about a topic for 15 minutes.
That's about five bucks for every 15 minutes you do that.
Do the video thing, you can get $5 for just five minutes.
And you can do it on just like five minutes of video
and you make $60 or $80 an hour
if you get the video thing.
So you just have to have a kind of good camera,
like at least 720.
And my microphones are not doing too good.
I don't know.
I always had microphone problems, you know?
Anyway, you can go look at my wall. It's called Babel. It's like a cool company
I found you have to apply just like I kind of audition like just it's really easy and then they pay cash cash up and stuff
because they're interested I
Think that's one of the things I would like to heavily promote because
They actually do pay off they're actually really good and I think people would enjoy it
So I can do a reading for Maya if she'd like, but I don't think she's here anymore. I don't know. It's gotten really quiet
Might take off for a while just come back tonight. I don't know I but I would like to maybe like
Somebody would like to get a longer reading
Or any other stuff you can schedule time with me, too. I have my email address on my
I paged or whatever.
I'm sorry, I'm not like the best shape today,
but I was up coding last night.
It's like, it takes a lot out of me.
I have a psyche burst going on.
I got people in the psyche burst.
Why don't we, we can go, we can go.
I think Trishalicious is a lot.
Everyone goes to say hi to Trishalicious, okay?
Say psyche, he said yeah.
I'll be back later, okay?
Muah.